let questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What is the correct syntax for an if statement in Python?",
    options: [
      "A.if (condition):",
      "B.if condition",
      "C.if: condition",
      "D.if condition:",
    ],
    answer: "D.if condition:",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is not a data type in JavaScript?",
    options: ["A.String", "B.Number", "C.Boolean", "D.ArrayList"],
    answer: "D.ArrayList",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is used to declare a variable in Java?",
    options: ["A.var", "B.let", "C.const", "D.int"],
    answer: "D.int",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is the correct syntax for a for loop in C#?",
    options: [
      "A.for i = 0 to 10",
      "B.for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)",
      "C.for (int i = 0; i <= 10)",
      "D.for i in range(0, 10)",
    ],
    answer: "B.for (i = 0; i <= 10; i++)",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is not a looping structure in PHP?",
    options: ["A.while", "B.for", "C.do-while", "D.foreach"],
    answer: "A.foreach",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Which of the following is not a valid operator in C++?",
    options: ["A.+", "B.-", "C.*", "D.$"],
    answer: "D.$",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question:
      "In which programming language is 'print' used for displaying output?",
    options: ["A.Python", "B.JavaScript", "C.Java", "D.C++"],
    answer: "A.Python",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "What is the correct syntax for a function in Ruby?",
    options: [
      "A.function name()",
      "B.def name",
      "C.function name",
      "D.def name()",
    ],
    answer: "D.def name()",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of variable in Swift?",
    options: ["A.Int", "B.String", "C.Double", "D.Object"],
    answer: "D.Object",
    category: "coding",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "In which programming language is '#' used for commenting?",
    options: ["A.Python", "B.JavaScript", "C.Java", "D.C++"],
    answer: "D.C++",
    category: "coding",
  },
];
